rumorscity.com 2013-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Rumors City

Your privacy is important to us. This policy covers how Rumors City uses personal information collected while you use the website. We will never share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties.

#### What we collect

As with most websites, Rumors City maintains a log of activity on its site. Your IP address will be recorded, along with other information which may or may not be supplied by your browser. This includes the address of the site that referred you to Rumors City, the type and version of the browser you are using, the operating system you use, and the screen resolution at which you viewed the site.

This information is used solely to help us improve our delivery of the services on the site. This may involve us or our external evaluators contacting you to follow up on any comments you have made.

#### Comments

Comments are welcomed and encouraged on this site, but there are some instances where comments will be edited or deleted as follows:

  * Comments deemed to be spam or questionable spam will be deleted. Including a link to relevant content is permitted, but comments should be relevant to the post topic.
  * Comments including profanity will be deleted.
  * Comments containing language or concepts that could be deemed offensive will be deleted.
  * Comments that attack a person individually will be deleted.

The owner of this site reserves the right to edit or delete any comments submitted to this site without notice. This comment policy is subject to change at anytime.

#### Cookies

When you visit the site, the pages you view, along with small text files called ‘cookies’, are downloaded onto your computer.

Each time you visit the site your computer will download a session cookie. This cookie only remains on your computer till you close your browser. This cookie is not used to identify you personally in anyway. We use session cookies to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how visitors use the site. This information helps us improve the sites structure and functionality.

You may opt to view our site without cookies by adjusting your browser’s settings. See your browser’s Help menu for information on how to do this. If you disable cookies some functions of the site may no longer work correctly.

The above information on how we use cookies applies to Rumors City services only. We do not have any control over cookies set by external websites (e.g. supplier websites).

Users have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on their browsers.

Rumors City is serious about protecting your privacy and personal information. Any information you supply to us may only be shared within the organisation.

Your personal details will not be supplied by Rumors City to any parties outside Rumors City or its partners or used for any purposes other than those listed above, unless we are required to do so by law.

#### Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies

The site displays context sensitive advertising from Google via Google’s AdSense program. We do not control the ads that appear, however they are clearly distinguishable as Google Ads.

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Rumors City users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
